Your little [ __ ] belongs to me.
I done said a lot of things in my day. I
admit it. This is payback in the way. I
regret it that I did it. I don't want a
couple Grammys, but I sold my soul to
get them. Wasn't in it for the trophies,
just a [ __ ] recognition. [ __ ] the
difference. I'm that crack up in the
law. [ __ ] the rules, man. I used to risk
it all. Now I got too much to lose. I've
been eating long enough, man. My stomach
should be full. I just ate. Lick the
plate. My buffet. Lucky me. [ __ ] you.
Thank
GB.
Nine G.
I got a couple of mansions. Still I
don't have any manners. You got a couple
of ghost riders, but to these kids it
don't actually matter. Asking me what
the [ __ ] happened to hip hop. I said I
don't have any answers cuz I took an L.
When I dropped my last album, it hurt me
like hell, but I'm back on these rappers
and actually coming from humble
beginnings. I'm someone uncomfortable
winning. I wish I could say what a
wonderful feeling. And we on the
upstream like we're punching the
ceiling, but nothing is feeling like
anyone has any [ __ ] ability to even
stick to a subject is killing me. The
inability to pin humility. Why don't we
make a bunch of [ __ ] songs about
nothing and mumble them? [ __ ] it. I'm
going for the jugular [ __ ] is a circus.
You clowns that are coming up. Don't
give an ounce of a [ __ ] about
the ones that were here before you that
made rap. Let's recap way back MC's that
wreak havoc on tape decks. Say that's
where the G raps and canes at. We need
three stacks sap and bring master ace
back cuz half of these rappers have
brain damage. Start a lean rapping face
tipped out like tree sap. I don't hate
trap. I don't want to seem mad but in
fact where the old me at the same cat
that would take that feedback and name
back. I need that but I think it's
inevitable. They know what button to
press or what lever to pull to give me
the snap though little [ __ ] And if I
pay it attention I'm probably making it
bigger but you've been taking your dicks
and I'm [ __ ] back ho. Get it on the
brink any minute. Got me thinking of
finishing everything with a sentiment
and reap been the benefits. I'mma sleep
at the will again as I be thinking about
an evil intent of another beat. I'm a
kill again. Cuz even if I got to end up
eating a pilligan, even ketamine
methamine with a minute, then it better
be at least 70. You're throwing a
milligram and I might as well cuz I'm
going to end up being a villain again. A
levels to the [ __ ] I got an elevator.
You can never say to me I'm not a
[ __ ] record breaker. I sound like a
broken record. Every time I break a
record if I break it, ever take away the
legacy I made, I never cater a
[ __ ] Now I got a right to be
this way. I got spons. But I roll till
the wheels fall off. I'm working
tirelessly. Hey, it's the moment y'all
been waiting for. Like California,
wishing rain to pour in that drought.
Y'all been praying for my downfall from
the 8 mile to the southpaw. Still the
same marshall the outlaw that they say
as a writer might have fell off. I'm
back on that bull like the cowboy. So
y'all got to move. Y'all got to move.
Yeah, y'all got to move. Give me some
room. Give me some room. Give me the
juice.
How about the cool? Hop out the cool.
Hop out the sho.
Y got to move.
Y got to move. Give me the juice.